So guys, if you want to do
SIP in mutual funds through Aaa Bank's iMobile application,
then keep watching this video completely.
In today's video, we have
told you how you can do SIP in your mutual fund from the comfort of your home using
your mobile phone using Aaa Bank's
iMobile application.
You know that
people get very good returns through SIP,
that is why many people do SIP.
SIP means Systematic
Investment Plan. We deposit a
fixed amount in any mutual fund through iMobile application, so that this
amount gets deducted from our account every month like RD
and gets added to the mutual fund.
We call it SIP and many
people also earn good returns from this.
If you do SIP in mutual funds through ICC Bank's iMobile application, then you will
not need any demarcated account for this.
You
can do SIP in mutual funds here without a demarcated account. Let's
start this video and understand the
whole process. Hello, my name is Manish
Prajapati. Welcome to all of you once again,
a new video.  If you're visiting my channel for the first
time, please subscribe. If you like the video,
please give it a like. So, to
do an SIP in mutual funds with ICC Bank, first you need to
download the iMobile application and
create an account there. If you already have an
account, you can log in.
This is the official mobile banking application of ICC Bank. When you
log in,
you'll
see an interface like this. Now, if you
want to do an SIP or invest in mutual funds,
you'll
get an option for DMA Mutual
Funds below. You'll have to click on it. When you
click on it, an
interface like this will appear. Here,
we'll first get the option for
mutual funds. Click on it once.
After that, some
coins will drop here, and you'll be taken to an interface like this.
If you're here for the first time and
click on the mutual fund option, it might
ask you to complete a risk profile.
You can select anything there
or choose your own.  You
can also see that this is a facility of ICICI Bank that
completes your risk profile,
in which ICICI Bank can suggest the best funds based on your risk profile.
So you can complete your risk profile here.
I have completed my profile.
Basically, here you have to select some questions on
how much income you have, how long you
want to invest for. After this, you will reach the ICC Bank
mutual fund page.
Now you can see here that you
can select many funds and from here you can do
SIP in mutual funds. For example,
here you can find equity funds,
index funds, tax-saver funds,
large cap funds.
Here you can select the fund as per your choice.
Look above, there
is also an option to search for funds. You
will click on the search option here and
from here you will enter the name of your fund
in which you want to invest your money. For example, to
show you, I searched here.
I wrote HSBC S, so
look here it has appeared.  HSBC Small Cap Fund
Growth: Here you can search for funds as per your choice.
All the funds of the fund you enter here are shown to you.
You can select the fund as per your choice.
For this, you can
seek advice from your financial advisor. You can
select the small cap fund from Google. If
you want to invest money in the fund,
then you will simply
click on the 'S' option here and
click on the 'OK' option here. Here you
can also select the fund by category.
For example, if someone wants to
invest money in an index fund, then if he
clicks on the 'Index Fund' option here, then
many
index funds will appear in front of you. Similarly,
if you want to invest money in a large fund, then
you will
click on 'Large Cap Fund' and
all the large cap funds will appear here. If
you click on the 'Buy' option, then
this type of option will appear here.
Here you will have to select whether you
want to do SIP in your fund or
LSM.  If you want to enter the amount, then
you get two-three options here, namely
Luxurious Amount SIP and FIP. This F
feature may seem new to you here, it
is best if you do not invest in it
because you do
not get compound interest here. So you will
click on the SIP option. After this, it will be
monthly, so you can make it monthly, quarterly
or weekly. If you
do it weekly, then money will be deducted from your account every week
and will be added to your fund. If
you do it monthly, then on a fixed date every month the
amount will be deducted from your account and will be
deposited in the fund. If you do it quarterly, then every quarter your money will be deducted here and will be deposited in this fund. The best option is monthly, so here I will click on the monthly option. After this, you will have to enter the amount
of minimum amount you
want to do SIP. So, it depends on each fund as to how much minimum amount
you
can do SIP in it. For example,
if I talk about this fund, then you can do at
least SIP in this fund.  You can start SIP from Rs 5500.
In some funds it will be Rs 1,
in some funds it will be Rs 000 as well, so you
can see it as per your convenience, so I will enter Rs 5000000,
after this you will get the option below,
New Folio on Folio Number, you will
leave it, after this there is an
option like this here, you will leave it here,
if you want to do SIP for a fixed time,
10 years, 20 years or 15, 20
years, whatever it is, then you can select your time here, according to
me,
this is the best option,
you will leave it, after this there
is an option of start date below, you
will click on it and here you will select a fixed date on
which your
SIP should be deducted from your account, here
you can select the date as per your convenience, you
can select the date on which your salary comes or you get your income, here if you do
not get the option to select the date like this, then
you  You can click here and
select the date in the next month, for example,
suppose your salary comes on the 10th,
then you will click on the 10th here,
after that you will simply click on the OK option, then
you will select all these here as per
your wish,
after this you will simply click on the Y Now option, then
this type of option will
appear there, you have to click on the OK option,
now here you get the
option to add a nominee, then it
asks you whether you want to add a nominee or not, then here it
automatically clicks on the No option,
you have to click on the Yes option here
and there is a pencil icon here, you have to
click on it, after this you will enter the name of the person whom
you want to make the nominee here,
click on the For you option below here, if the nominee
is a minor then click on the Yes option,
you can enter the name of his father etc. If the nominee is 18 plus then
click on the No option and here  You
will select who is your nominee and what is their
relation. Below there is an option for share
percentage, so you will make it
100% by clicking here. Below you will enter the complete address of the nominee.
After this you will click on the simple save
option here,
from here your nominee will be added. After this there is an
option to enter the employee ID,
this is optional. If there is someone
you know who works in a bank, then
you can enter his/her employee ID,
otherwise you can skip it.
After this you will click on the simple save option here.
Now
an OTP will come on the registered mobile number of your ICICI Bank account,
enter it. After this you will
click on the submit option here,
from here your SIP will be completed and
you will get the folio number etc. from here. If
you want, you can take a screenshot or photo of it.
Now as soon as your SIP is
done, it will not be shown here intentionally,
you have to wait somewhere.
After three working days, your SIP
amount will be shown here.  It will be
how much is its value, how much amount you have increased or
decreased, how much percentage return you have got,
all this will be shown to you here, you
can see it here, if you want to see your portfolio, then
here you get the option of view portfolio,
you will click on it and
here you will see your investment in this way,
you can cancel the SIP by
clicking on the three lines,
we will make a detailed video on this, how
you stop your SIP here, in
this way you can start SIP
in mutual fund through mobile application in ICICI Bank,
if you
liked our information then like the video,
let's meet in the next video